Echika Raphael

A Work Loving Software Developer with 2 years of experience who is comfortable with React, JavaScript, HTML/CSS and responsive web design to deliver customer experience with proven experience in creating and designing software in a test-driven environment.

EXPERIENCES

BEELRAPH COMPUTER INSTITUTE, LAGOS

MAY 2020 -AUG 2022

Student

Learned computer courses to help me develop skills and knowledge Employed by professional programmers

Designed a website and worked closely with my mentor.

Assisted in creating a website with the use of Tailwind CSS - A CSS framework

Learned React - A JavaScript library for building user interfaces and carried out series of capstone projects to test my skills

Worked as a team leader for the Public Speaking course that took place through the period of my learning phase.

Side Hustle Internship, Nigeria — Software Development and Public Speaking

MAY 2021 - DEC 2021

Present for more than 95% of the live classes

Worked as a team leader for the Public Speaking course that took place through the period of my Internship.

Contributed to 10% of the team codebase

Designed a website and worked closely with my mentor.

Assisted in creating a website with the use of Tailwind CSS - A CSS framework

Learned React - A JavaScript library for building user interfaces.

7, Ekoro Road, Lagos, Nigeria. **+234 708 570 6889**

echikaraphael@gmail.com

GITHUB DEPLOYMENTS

Portfolio website

https://echika.github.io/portf olio-website/

A fashion website

https://echika.github.io/fashi on

An age calculator app https://echika.github.io/agecalc

A todo app

https://echika.github.io/todoapp/

MY GITHUB ACCOUNT Check my repositories here: https://github.com/Echika

CONNECT WITH ME

MY LINKEDIN ACCOUNT

https://www.linkedin.com/in/echika-raphael-b07b96216

MY INSTAGRAM ACCOUNT

https://instagram.com/rapha elechika

MY TWITTER ACCOUNT

https://twitter.com/@echika_raphael

CORE TECHNOLOGIES

HTML AND CSS

JavaScript

React JS

ZURI Internship, Nigeria — Software Development

MAY 2022 - AUG 2022

Intern

Created my resume.

Learned CSS Layouts - Grid and Flex boxes

Used my knowledge of Javascript to create an interactive page.

Created my first website using advanced knowledge of HTML and CSS.

Created a mimicry of the Zuri homepage.

HNG Internship, Nigeria — Software Development

SEP 2022 - NOV 2022

Intern

Created my resume.

Learned CSS Layouts - Grid and Flex boxes

Used my knowledge of Javascript to create an interactive page.

Created my first website using advanced knowledge of HTML and CSS.

Created a mimicry of the Zuri homepage.

EDUCATION

ANGLICAN GRAMMAR SCHOOL, OGUN STATE, NIGERIA. SSCE

BEELRAPH COMPUTER INSTITUTE, LAGOS

WEB DEVELOPMENT.

Material UI

Tailwind CSS

BootStrap

SOFT SKILLS

Emotional Intelligence

Leadership Skills

Strong Work Ethics

Teamwork

Great communication skills

Adaptability

AWARDS

Side hustle Certificate

Jobberman Certificate

ZURI Certificate

HNG Certificate

Most hardworking group leader at Beelraph Computer

Institute

LANGUAGES

Fluent English, Yoruba